(Prof Sharpe:)He was convinced that calorie
restriction was the key
(Prof Sharpe:)to living forever.
(Raj:)Does it work?
(Howard:)Seriously?
(Raj:)Well, he could have been hit
by a bus. You don't know.
(Prof Sharpe:)Sorry it's not more interesting.
(Prof Sharpe:)On the bright side,
you didn't have to listen
(Prof Sharpe:)to his stomach growl
for 35 years.
(Leonard:)So, was there anything
that Professor Abbott worked on
(Leonard:)during his life that came close
to an accomplishment?
(Prof Sharpe:)To be honest, his research
never amounted to anything.
(Howard:)Oh.
You were his
colleague.
(Raj:)How did your research turn out?
(Raj:)Great. Hey, this is
the apartment you get
(Raj:)when you win a Nobel.
(Raj:)Well, you could be very frugal.
(Raj:)I'm getting a little tired
of everybody's sarcasm.
(Bernadette:)I'm not a bully.
(Bernadette:)I mean, maybe I come
off a little strong,
(Bernadette:)but that's only because my
dad raised me to be tough
(Bernadette:)and not to take
crap from anybody.
(Penny:)No. That's fine, but there's
a difference between being tough
(Penny:)and telling your friend her new
pants look like a saggy diaper.
(Bernadette:)I did say that, didn't I?